



Summary

I am an experienced Childcare Worker with an excellent history of working in the non-profit industry. I previously attended and graduated from Penn State University in 2007 where I majored in Information Science and Technology. There I learned how to code in C++ and Javascript; how to write HTML, XML and CSS; and last but not least the importance of a good UX/UI . In May of 2019 I completed a Udemy online course, *The Complete Web Developer in 2019: Zero to Mastery,* which taught front-end and backend development. My skills are in Express.js, Node.js, React.js, Javascript, HTML, and CSS. My goal is to further hone my problem-solving and analytical skills as they will help me to write and debug code better. I look forward to joining a company in which I can become a valuable asset and contributing member to a team.



Experience

Oct 2011 - present

Childcare/Mental Health Worker

Silver Springs/Martin Luther School, Plymouth Meeting, PA

- Organize educational activities during the day for kids who have not yet started school.
- Supervise a pleasant wake-up routine for all children on the residential unit.
- Communicate health needs or concerns to the nurse and/or Executive-On-Duty (EOD).
- Tolerate behavior that is defiant and aggressive. Use SCM techniques (may include physical redirection and passive physical restraint) when situations warrant in accordance with SS/MLS policies, procedures and applicable Commonwealth regulations.
- Communicate with other departments as necessary (i.e. Health Care, Food Service, Martin Luther School, etc.).
- Maintain strict confidentiality, as required by Commonwealth regulations, law and SS/MLS policies.

Jun 2007 -Jun 2010

Field Technician

Comcast, Philadelphia, PA

- Provides tech support for all equipment installed at customers' residences
- Performs custom installation work including wall fishing, post wiring, etc.
- Ensures all jobs are completed as instructed by customers' demands
- Manages issues and resolutions in a timely manner

Jun 2005 -Jun 2007

Head of IT

Global Construction Technologies Inc., Philadelphia, PA

- Coordinates IT operations for company
- Implements remedial processes to help improve business functions



Education

Jan 2018 -May 2019

The Complete Web Developer in 2019: Zero to Mastery, Udemy Online Course

- Taught skills in Javascript, React.js, Node.js, Express.js, HTML, and CSS
- · Coursework in both front-end and back-end development
- Problem-solving and debugging

Sep 2003 -May 2007

Pennsylvania State University, University Park, PA

- B.S. in Information Science and Technology
- Focus on Integration and Application



Address

240 West Walnut Lane

Apt. C300

Philadelphia, PA 19144

Phone

267-880-8942

E-mail

yujirojenkins@gmail.com

Date of birth

09 May 1985

Facebook

www.facebook.com/Ty-Yuji

Instagram

www.instagram.com/spacemanci

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ty-jenkins/



Javascript

React.js

Express.js

Node.js

PostgreSQL

HTML

CSS